優しい陽だまりにチャイムがディレイする
頬を撫でる風 息吹は深くなってく
遠回りの涙 名前つけた明日 重なる未来のノーライン
あどけないこんな気持ちも
はじけ飛ぶほど笑い合えた日も
大切に育てていけるように
途切れ途切れの時を越えて
たくさんの初めて遅れた
繋がってゆけ 届け
繋がってゆけ
届け
甘す
Wait, when did she...
Te-teleportation?
I kicked it.
Good work, you're a beast.
Keep that up when we might have a chance on field day, like for real.
It was worth buying that red t-shirt after all.
A compliment.
The truth is, I didn't learn that move on my own.
It was Kaze Haya who taught it to me.
Please let this reach for me.
To you.
Nice one.
You kicked it right on target.
Reached right to me.
Try it again, just like that.
But this time, kick the ball after stopping it first.
Don't have to rush it.
Cool.
One more.
Okay.
Over here.
Pass it to me.
Here.
Jeez.
Go around.
Nice.
Yes.
Yeah.
Reached right to me.
so hot I'm gonna wait till I stop sweating and then get out of these
clothes you can head back to the classroom first Satoko
it's empty I guess no one's come back yet huh do you know of Kaze Haya's here
this girl she's that French no it's Karumi sorry but the boys haven't come back from
the field day practice so now oh really it's amazing how she just talks to me
normally what a nice person she kind of reminds me of Kaze Haya hey huh you
probably don't remember this but you helped me pick out some handouts I
dropped that really was super kind of you thanks huh no that's just what
anybody would do right but if you keep thanking me like this you're gonna make
me blush she's such a super friendly person and she's such a feminine aura the
girl I've always wanted to be he's right in front of me
oh seriously the more I look at her the more she looks just like a doll
what that was just inside my head how did it get out it didn't I was the one who
said that hmm Sawako Kuro Numa that's your name my real name wait did she just say a doll
and yeah of course I remember that time with the handouts cuz I remember I looked at you and
I thought she looks just like a doll looks just like a doll looks just like a doll looks just like a doll looks just like a doll
hey crew me if we don't head out to the playing field soon we're gonna be late
okay I'll come back again later
she really is just like that doll with the growing hair you look just like a doll that's a new one no
one's ever said that to me in my whole life did something happen Sadako what's up it's pretty obvious
your head's floating somewhere in the clouds right now I kind of had someone compliment me just now
actually really like how they said I look like a doll
oh
Sawa Sawa Sawa Sawa I'm your Sawa doll that's a compliment no I seriously doubt it was
that's hot after that don't you think we can win this oh yeah there's no doubt my mind now sure about that
oh I thought something felt different about him it's that he's not wearing his vest
tell me how's the girl's side ah no complaints here Sadako's new skills have really upped our game
oh they have yeah seriously that's so awesome
all right
Kasehaya Kurumi stopped by to see you earlier oh did she appreciate it
but why about field day committee stuff maybe I see Kurumi's on the committee too
wait did you say you met Kurumi after I left you to get changed Yoshida
ah you just called me Yoshida again
I mean can we really complain when we're still calling her Sadako
wait you're right it's difficult to suddenly switch the way you refer to someone
right Sadako gets it well there's no need to force it then at least
huh Sawako Kuronuma that's your name that reminds me the next time I get a chance to talk to her
maybe I'll try being more friendly I'll say what's up Kurumi
oh on that note Ryu huh did you manage to remember Sadako's full name
Takako Kuruyama
so close just a little bit more and you'd have had it Ryu
not too bad considering it's Ryu you're talking about
I was so confident
I'm Kuronuma a pleasure
hey Kasehaya why don't you show him how it's done
huh huh yeah show Ryu a good example
Sawako Kuronuma oh not bad not bad
next how about you try calling her just by her first name this time
but why
practice
Sawako's not very good at interacting with people on a first name basis
so getting her used to it would really help her out
I think that it'd be a cool one
Hmm
hmm
ha
I can't!
I get it. It was just a joke after all.
Anxiety...
That was so nerve-wracking.
My heart is...
Actually, now that I think about it, I've been nervous since the other day.
If anything, it seems like I'm even more nervous than I was before.
Oh, it's Kasehaya!
Oh yeah, you're right.
You know the name of the girl he's talking to? She's cute.
Seriously? You're saying that in front of me?
Besides, you and Kurumi wouldn't make a good match anyway.
What?
Yeah, those two are perfect for each other.
Yeah, I see what you mean, but...
Well, I was still interested in borrowing that thing.
I see it too.
Huh? Oh yeah, that's right, the CD.
Man, I totally forgot. My bad.
Aw, jeez.
Oh, I just told you too.
I'll be sure to bring it tomorrow.
Oh, nice.
I'm sorry, okay?
Alright, alright.
Promise I won't forget.
Maybe I should try being more like her.
Fluffy.
You think a perm would look good on me?
Hmm?
A fluffy one.
A perm?
Sha-cha!
The heck was that?
Something weird just popped in my mind.
Speaking of hair, what made you choose your current style?
Uh, uh, I thought if it was long it would be more feminine.
And I'm a really big fan of girly things.
Ah, gotcha.
Then how about keeping the length as is, but lightening the color?
Yeah, that's nice. Soft light brown hair.
That sounds good.
Brown hair.
Oh, uh, uh, has a background character vibe to it.
But what if she added a little bit of curl to it?
Chain smoker?
So how about adding layers, then?
Classic Yankee?
You know what? The hairstyle you have now was perfect.
Oh, really?
Totally. In fact, you should just stick with it for the rest of your life.
Mm-hmm.
Goodbye, then, Fluffy.
I shall stay this way for the remainder of my days.
Anyway, haven't you had that same cut since forever ago?
Uh, yeah, more or less.
Why did you suddenly think of getting a perm?
Uh, I just thought Fluffy was much cuter.
Oh, so it was about wanting to become cuter.
Y-yes.
It's not because someone told me I looked like a doll or anything.
I mean, that made me happy,
but I'm not gonna let it get to my head, so...
Right.
Yeah, we know.
What? Training after school?
Need a ball? Why don't you borrow one from Pin?
Hey, good idea.
If I'm being honest with myself, I was envious.
Kurumi is so incredibly cute.
I couldn't help but feel jealous.
I wonder what it's like
to be cute enough to catch anyone's attention,
and I find myself wishing
that I could be like that.
I'll never be exactly like her.
I fully understand that.
But maybe I can become cuter
in my own way.
Sadako!
Hirana, Enda!
Ekko, Tomo, okay?
Uh, uh, uh, Ekko and...
T-Tomo...
So were you about to train on your own?
Uh-huh.
Ch-Chizu and Ayane went to borrow a ball for me,
so I'm just waiting for them right now.
Ball?
Yeah, they said Mr. Orion might be able to lend us one.
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha.
Sure, I'll allow it.
If it's to win us first place,
take five or ten.
As many as you want.
One is more than enough.
Yeah, let's go!
Aw, yeah!
First place!
Let's destroy them!
Go!
What is this?
Huh? But wait a sec.
Echo, didn't you say that Ayana is going to do volleyball with you?
Apparently there's a bunch of ways to practice if you had three more people doing it.
So Ayana offered to help me out too.
I see. That's so nice.
Let's do our best for field day.
Let's do it.
We really are friends, aren't we?
Kazehaya!
Hey, what's up? It's been a while, man.
I know, it has.
K-Kazehaya!
It seems like someone's always coming up to talk to him.
He's so popular. Must be fun.
Oh yeah, Kazehaya. The two of you weren't together then, huh?
Well, I had the field day committee meeting, that's why.
Ha, gotcha. So you're pretty busy then.
Was there anyone on the committee we went to middle school with?
Yeah. Kurumi.
He calls her by her first name.
Now that I think of it, I don't think I've ever heard Kazehaya refer to a girl by her first name before.
That was the first time.
I can't!
But saying hers came so naturally.
They must be really close.
What the heck was that just now?
That's right.
I've never asked him about it before.
But I wonder if Kazehaya has someone that's special to him.
Is using first names that kind of special?
My heart aches.
Ku-ro-numa?
Practice again today?
But then again, just looking at his face might be the thing that's making my heart ache.
Wha-what?
It aches. It won't stop.
miedo角度 vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault vault user vault vault vault vault
Just now, right before Kurumi called out to him, he was about to say something, wasn't he?
What are you two doing? I want in!
We were just...
We weren't really doing anything.
What do you mean? You're funny.
I see. It was in my head. There was nothing going on.
Of course, right? I must be overthinking things. I'm being silly.
It's hot in here.
When it comes to Kazuhaya, I'm just too hypersensitive.
Oh, Sawako, you're sweating like crazy.
I'm suddenly nervous.
She really is a nice person.
Uh, thank you.
Mm-mm.
There. All good.
I think... I may have become her fan just now.
Huh. I had no idea they became so close.
Oh, that's right. Was there something you needed?
Mm-mm. Not really. I just came over to talk to Sawako.
Definitely a fan.
Since the two of us have become friends, after all.
Right, Sawako?
Mm-hmm. I'm your fan...
FRIEN...
Yeah, we're friends.
I mean, obviously, right?
Friends...
Friends?
That's it.
Thank you.
A frustrating atmosphere. An awkward exchange of words. Next time, working together.